<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">SlideUpSample</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="text_sample">VHS cillum food truck tumblr. Ennui pour-over cardigan aute, tattooed et laboris american apparel 
        fingerstache shoreditch keffiyeh id pop-up direct trade. Eu echo park ullamco, pork belly wes anderson trust fund synth 
        PBR viral letterpress lo-fi Austin exercitation butcher. Nostrud retro skateboard eu four loko you probably haven\'t heard 
        of them, leggings Austin single-origin coffee. Aesthetic banksy readymade pop-up, delectus elit trust fund. Mixtape proident 
        cosby sweater consequat adipisicing. Occaecat dreamcatcher enim, put a bird on it consequat qui duis occupy seitan. 
        Tofu sunt pour-over, dreamcatcher art party next level butcher stumptown chambray dolore. Echo park banksy carles mcsweeney\'s
         art party tempor ex placeat aliquip pour-over food truck. Fanny pack pork belly tofu yr, salvia seitan typewriter kale chips et 
         gluten-free minim magna direct trade labore. Aliquip cupidatat do mcsweeney\'s cliche swag, farm-to-table dolor sartorial 
         exercitation et ennui raw denim artisan. Ethical whatever vegan mollit. Reprehenderit synth typewriter, banh mi mcsweeney\'s 
         esse cardigan gluten-free nulla ut proident consequat sint. Qui ea vice irony exercitation, mlkshk labore photo booth +1 cred VHS.</string>
    <string name="sample_header">This is my own content</string>
    <string name="sample_subheader">An this is a little text to show a little description</string>

    <string-array name="sample_names_list">
        <item>Alberto</item>
        <item>Alonso</item>
        <item>Brian</item>
        <item>Carlos</item>
        <item>Cesar</item>
        <item>Daniel</item>
        <item>Dany</item>
        <item>Dionisio</item>
        <item>Ernesto</item>
        <item>Esteban</item>
        <item>Francisco</item>
        <item>Franklin</item>
        <item>Gabriel</item>
        <item>Hernan</item>
        <item>Ivan</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>